familytime.com 2017-12-03

# FamilyTime.com - Privacy Page

**What is our mission?**   
FamilyTime's mission is to help you save time and money by helping you organize your household activities. We do this by providing useful planning tools and by getting the best of web offers and practical content for your family. We do the surfing, so you save time to be with your family. To do this well, we become a trusted partner to you. We will not sell or give individual data about you to third parties. 

**Is there a cost?**   
The FamilyTime Site is offered as a free service. It is paid for by advertisers and sponsors who want you to know about their products and services. We will use certain registration and tracking data, as outlined below, to make your experience using FamilyTime more enjoyable and more valuable to you by screening certain ads and offers. 

**What happens to your stored information?   
**One key powerful feature of the FamilyTime Site is that you can store information about your family in a central location on the Internet. This gives you and your family the convenience and power of accessing, for example, a family calendar and updating it from any PC on the Internet when you are at work, at school, or traveling. 

We make every reasonable effort to safeguard that data for you and to assure that it will be there when you need it. All of the information that you put into any FamilyTime application (calendar, recipes file cabinet, etc.) about your family is your own. The information is backed up on our servers to help protect against loss, and it is NOT made available by us to any third party in any form. You can remove the information at any time by deleting it or canceling your registration with us. All FamilyTime services are furnished AS IS, subject to the Limitations of Liability and EXCLUSION OF WARRANTIES set forth in our Terms and Conditions of Use. Please review those Terms and Conditions for further details. 

**Do we use the information that you store in the FamilyTime program?**   
As stated above, the areas provided to store personal data, are just that - storage areas - and are NOT used in any way to direct ads or offers to you. Corporate Sponsorships are offered for FamilyTime sections based on the general subject area of the section, not on your personal information held within any section. None of the individual data in any of these sections is given or sold to a third party by FamilyTime. 

Data that you generate in collecting recipes, creating menus, and creating shopping lists is aggregated to help us and our sponsors understand what foods, menus, and products are most popular. The data is never used in a manner that can be traced to an identified individual. 

**What information does the FamilyTime Site need at registration?**   
We require one name and email address for each family at the time of registration. In addition, we require zip code to provide you with relevant local offers. We will email you to let you know about new features or other offers of interest from FamilyTime, or to address customer needs and requests. Other family members can use the FamilyTime site without registering as long as they have access to the family password. Other data collected at registration is used to direct relevant ads and information to you as part of using FamilyTime. 

**What are "cookies" and how does the FamilyTime Site use them?**   
We track your visit to our site by giving you a "cookie." Cookies are pieces of information that Web sites transfer to your computer's hard drive for record keeping purposes. They make the creation of the FamilyTime application possible by allowing the site to save preferences and remember what operations you have completed. Cookies also help FamilyTime collect anonymous click stream data for tracking user trends and patterns.   
The use of cookies is now quite common, and you'll find them used on most major Web sites. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies. If you prefer, you can reset your browser either to notify you when you've received a cookie, or to refuse to accept cookies. You should understand that FamilyTime will not function properly, if you set your browser to reject cookies.

**Third-Party Advertiser and "Cookies"**   
We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/).

**What happens to information you give to Advertisers?**   
If you leave the Site via a link to an advertiser, coupon provider or other merchant, you will then be subject to the privacy policy on that company's web site. It is up to you to investigate the policy of any other site(s) you visit, via links or otherwise, to decide which sites you wish to visit, and to decide what information, if any, you wish to provide on those sites. 

**Does FamilyTime share information?**   
Except as described in this privacy policy, FamilyTime will never willfully disclose individually identifiable information about its users to any third party without first receiving that user's permission. 

**Children Under 13**   
FamilyTime cares about protecting the privacy of children. We won't knowingly allow anyone under 13 to provide us any personal identifying information (such as name, email address or phone number). If you're under 13, please do not register with FamilyTime or provide us with any personal identifying information in compliance with the [Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act](http://www.ftc.gov/privacy/privacyinitiatives/childrens.html). 

**How do you "Opt-out"?**   
You will always be asked if you want to receive messages from FamilyTime. Even if you opt-in to a program, you will be offered the ability to opt-out of receiving information by email or mailing via following directions included with each correspondence. 

**Notification of Changes**   
If at some point in the future, there is a change to our information usage practices that affect your Personally Identifiable Information, we will notify you by email of the relevant changes. At the time of this message, you will be able to opt-out of this information usage by sending a message to the following email: [customerservices@familytime.com](mailto:customerservices@familytime.com). You should also check this posted privacy statement for changes. We welcome any questions or comments you have, please direct them to [customerservices@familytime.com](mailto:customerservices@familytime.com) or write to Customer Services, FamilyTime LLC, 101 Merritt Blvd., Trumbull, CT06611, (203) 610-8270. 

Your experience and privacy are very important to us and we respect your rights.  
FamilyTime
